hi everyone on this video we are going
to talk about the manulife online
website for policyholders
[Music]
once you get the plan in manual life you
will receive an email of your policy
number so in order to track your
premiums your policy details and
everything you can log in in order to
register just go to
online.manylife.com.ph
and then click register now
input your email address country code
mobile number
date of birth month and year and read
the terms and conditions and the privacy
policy and then pick this checkbox in
order to agree then just click continue
once you've registered then you will
receive
your registration details and then you
can sign in okay since i already have my
account i'm going to sign in
and
okay let's just sign in
okay
and then pick
how you want to receive your otp i'm
going to pick through mobile
once you're in you can see your policies
and the details of your policy about you
okay
here you can browse your portfolio so
aside from the policies you can see some
other documents so
um if you click
your policy you can just click this
to view the details
so here you can see the type of plan i
have policy number name of the insured
the details of the plan
and when
i started my plan when is the expiration
date what benefits do i get
so my beneficiaries
you can even see down here who your
agent is your insurance agent is our
financial advisor and her or his updated
contact details
okay you may also download and access
your receipts
and
other documents here
so fun details this is the value of your
account if you get a vol or
variable universal life
policy
as you can see here this is the total
fund value
and
on which fund you are
invested in
okay
you can also view the other funds right
here
payment details
you can see when your last payment was
and when is your next due date for me i
am
paying throughout a debit so
i won't need to worry when to pay my
premiums it just automatically debits
from my account
you can see it here and the previous
transactions
key
if you want to claim you can just click
this button
and
here you will view the
forms that you need to fill up when you
want to claim
okay so
all the forms are here
if you have any questions you can ask
your connection advisor or
go to ph customer care
you can also check the frequently asked
questions over here
you can also check your payments
if you want to pay your premiums i am
going to show you how to do that in a
separate video profile
view your profile
[Music]
if you want to double check if all your
information is correct or if you want to
edit it you may do so
account settings
okay policy address
addresses
double check if you're here
details are correct and update as needed
okay so it's a really easy website to
browse
by the way if you click this you're
being directed to the manulife website
which can be accessible even if you
don't have any account to know more just
go to this website
that's it guys it's as simple as that
it's very straightforward and user
friendly if you'd like to know more
please comment down below if you have
any questions also please comment down
below i'd appreciate it if you like this
video hit the subscribe button and the
notification bell in order to be
notified on more videos similar to these
thank you guys bye
[Music]
you